Okay, thank you.
First of all, I would like to thank Claude for inviting us to share some of the results of our school and students.
Today, I hope to introduce some of the projects we are doing in fashion and 3D design in Hong Kong,
as well as some of the projects and methods of their students that they can share with different audiences and listeners.
Today, I have divided into three different sharing processes.
The first one is a competition with Claude in Hong Kong.
The second one is on the campus.
We have some examples and some projects that we have collaborated with Hong Kong designers.
And the third one is about recruiting and learning.
Okay, thank you.
This is our school, Hong Kong Design Academy.
We are in Hong Kong.
And I am Asa.
I am in charge of the 3D fashion design.
Thank you.
Next slide, please.
Yes.
This is our competition with Claude in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong Design Academy held its first Closed 3D competition in Hong Kong in 2022.
We hope that students can try on a set of clothes,
and then we hope that they can use their creativity and the whole process
to start from scratch,
and then use their creativity and their ideas to make a 3D dress.
Next slide, please.
This is a video.
We turned 10 different students' ideas into animation.
This was done a few years ago.
Closed 3D is a 2020 competition.
So in the beginning,
We put their ideas in there.
We didn't think about the compte or manufacturing aspect at all.
Next slide, please.
Last slide, please.
Yes.
Next slide, please.
It was a competition for our students to try on 3D clothes.
Right.
For a very small amount of money that won from hire three youths,
We camealleys gave them a proof from our source material so that they can raise their seventy thousand dollars.
So in the beginning, we only wanted them to use their own ideas.
We didn't have too much production or process.
The next step is the school's next step, which is waste.
Because in 3D, we can quickly create a 3D process.
We can quickly know their ideas.
But in the place where there is a lot of waste in the fabric,
we also thought that if we could give some materials provided by the cloth factory
to CLO to test,
then the students can use the board and some of the fabric properties at the beginning.
It can be more accurate.
And it can be faster to design a cloth.
Yes, next.
Thank you.
This is our zero waste project.
We hope that students and different teams
will also consider the use of some board and materials
in the design process and try their best to achieve the zero waste.
Because in CLO or many other places,
and other components.
We can see the use of the fabric very clearly,
and also the design,
whether the whole fabric has been used up.
Finally, we put the student's fabric
and some teaching methods
into our school.
This is another one we just talked about.
We also hope to cooperate with some local Hong Kong designers.
This is Kim Yen,
a Hong Kong designer.
She is also a semifinalist of LVMH this year.
This project or cooperation
is that we take some environmental materials from the factory,
and then we take them for testing.
Then Kim Yen, the designer,
draws their patterns on the fabric.
Then the students design one piece of clothing
through this fabric and this pattern,
which is the 3D garment on our right hand side.
Then which rectangular shape in the middle?
This rectangular shape
is the sample when they made the pattern.
This is the sample.
The entire rectangular shape has been used up.
There is no waste of any part.
Then the print.
This is our final product.
Then on the left hand side,
you can see that another student's design
has also used up the entire fabric.
On the right hand side,
you can see a real garment.
We display it in our school's archive.
It is a girl in the museum.
Then we also turn the student's work
and some 3D garments
into the animation of the next page.
Because we are thinking
that in the 3D clothes,
we can also make some animation
in the 4D process.
So that everyone knows
how exciting it is.
Then how to turn from 1 to 1
into a complete fabric
is also one of our ideas.
It's not just about showing some results.
There are also some processes
that can be used a lot in clothes.
Then we can see
how to turn from fabric
to 1 to 1.
That's it.
Another thing is
the same idea,
but it starts from the fabric.
From one piece of clothing
to one piece of fabric.
It starts from the beginning of the cloth,
but they also have a connection.
Because we also think that in reality,
it is more difficult for us to show such a process and some ideas.
We can't make two pieces and then open all the pieces.
So in the code, it is a great advantage
to give us the ability to show some process.
Thank you.
In addition, there are some teaching and learning parts.
In the next page, you can see that I divided the code 3D
and some digital directions into four different stages.
The first one is more basic.
They learn how to use Claw.
The second stage is another stage.
It is to separate different parts.
It could be a sweater, it could be a cowboy.
The third one is to take different applications,
it could be Claw's rendering, it could be a propaganda image,
and match them.
The fourth one is to use AI to create a different look.
The last one is our more important PA project.
In the first page, I just talked about the more basic ones.
They learn how to use Claw's design tools,
and how to use them to make clothes.
It could be sewing.
There are some fabrics.
How to insert some patterns.
Then the next one is students' homework.
It is more focused on some creativity.
They can use different lights.
They can have a cat-like look.
They can do what they want with Claw in their hearts.
But it may be different from some of the practices in reality.
There are different ways to use them.
And some of the prescriptions are differently did.
But although the first one was fundamental to our knowledge.
And the second one was more of a partial product.
Also, when it comes to first stage, 따pping.
In addition, we have a collaboration with Advanced Stadium.
Every year, we have a collaboration with Advanced Stadium.
They will give some oxen cloth to our students to use.
And then, they will print it.
In the second stage, it is a bit more complicated.
They may have to control the properties of the cloth.
So, the oxen cloth and the oxen cloth,
as well as some stone water, puckering, and other things,
are a bit more advanced.
This is a 3D oxen cloth that we worked on with the students last year.
In the summer, two other students participated in Advanced Stadium
in Shanghai.
Which one?
The one that is shown here.
In the next page, we have a video.
The three of them turned their work into a 3D oxen cloth.
Yes.
In addition, the oxen cloth I just mentioned.
We have several different courses.
In the design of this oxen cloth,
our school has some Syrinsharki APEX design tools.
They will design some oxen cloth patterns and colors in APEX.
Then, they will do a simulation.
Then, I will ask them to put the patterns they want into the oxen cloth,
and make a draft.
They have to imagine,
and they have to be responsible for not only a 3D pattern,
but also the wool they use,
and the appearance they really make when they sew it.
How to match their pattern.
The next one is one of the lessons.
In addition to a large cloth pattern,
and what we call Fully Fashioned,
which is the original pattern of wool,
we will also give it to the students.
The students will also use some more traditional painting methods
to draw the patterns they want.
Then, in APEX,
design their draft.
Then, put it into the mold,
and then make a real cloth.
It's in the bottom part.
The one on the right is
for the students to wear their own design of wool.
These are also some samples,
that is, what students will use when doing homework.
This is the second stage.
In the next stage,
the third one is how to put things inside,
which may be some accessories,
handbags, and clothes,
can be placed in different tools to be applied together.
In the next page,
usually when we complete a cloth in CLO,
we can use their render,
the rendering part.
And then,
when AI is more popular,
and more convenient,
we can put some render patterns in CLO,
and put them together.
It's like a page.
From the model,
and the things she wears,
lighting, background,
we can also use AI to generate.
But the real clothes,
and accessories,
we can use AI to put them together for us.
It's more convenient,
and a little bit faster.
Because when we use AI,
we use some of the clouds.
If we use local CLO,
maybe do some research,
the requirements of the computer are a little bit higher.
Maybe it's better to use GPU.
But AI can help us
to collect some more complex,
and maybe it's a long-term presentation.
And then this is an example of a lesson.
It can be turned into different degrees,
have different lights.
Maybe we can also make,
students can make his work
into a video.
Just like this.
But the whole idea
is not part of the production process.
They don't have to think about
whether the real production
is the same as this.
Because this is just using some technology
to match some 3D ideas,
some of our ideas.
And then the other stage
is the graduation stage.
Their graduation project
is from the development,
and the final result.
We all hope that CLO3D
can help them
to use their ideas.
Yes.
Starting from the next page,
we can see the students' works.
Their ideas are also
used in some traditional ways
to imagine and use.
They use Google
or different websites
to find some different images
and put them together
as a starting point.
And then in the next part,
they can spend
the style they want
and the look of the board.
But in the middle of the development process,
we can use CLO3D
to make some sincere boards.
Like this girl,
she has some kind of
flying scarf.
And then the call function
and the PIN function
and the FEAST function
can help her
to complete her ideas.
There are some differences
in the reality.
And then in the next page,
the final design.
The one on the right
is a 3D design
that she made.
And then,
in my opinion,
it's the same as
his thoughts and reality are almost the same.
Because in the next page, you can see
the left side is the model wearing his clothes.
And he is also with Lansing, which is our cooperation.
He has won some local awards,
like the Young Taylor Award in the middle,
and some graduate awards.
He also won a championship.
And then there are other students
how to use clothes in their works.
It seems that this girl is also the same.
Complete a simple sample in clothes,
then print it out and make it into a real sample.
The other one is that he re-paints it,
and then in clothes,
another one is made into a board.
In addition, the one on the far right is the result of an effort.
He also used clothes and his last work
to participate in a local 4G competition,
the last 10 games.
This is also a sample.
This is also their mock-up,
which is the look of the board.
These two slides are the same.
Because we think clothes rendering
and the benefits of clothes board
is that we teachers can see their designs more easily.
From left to right,
just like the traditional front and back,
we also have this proportion.
It's easier to know their ideas.
And then we also have this proportion.
And it's easier to produce.
Then the last one is to share is the competition.
In our school,
there are some subjects and some classes in the desert.
They use clothes,
but in some competitions,
it may be some competitions for fur.
And this is a uniform of the Hong Kong team's full-fledged club.
They also use clothes to match their ideas.
So we think that using clothes,
whether it's a sweater or a sweater,
is actually very good
to let students express a more complete design.
And then the most important thing is not just 3D,
it's because we are doing fashion design,
which is fashion design.
We hope that we can produce it,
which is the same as we originally thought.
So we are now aiming to connect the 3D and 1D parts together.
It's like a digital twin.
This is what we did with some of the students and schools
in the past few years.
Thank you.
Oh,
I have people's backs.
I'll join them.
Our class two siesta has come
up,
are you ready?
Yes,
I'm ready for the last thought,
By the way-
By the way,